thebitcoinnews.co.uk 2014-08-22

# Privacy Policy | The Bitcoin News - Decentralised Bitcoin and Crypto News

**PRIVACY POLICY**

**1.        Our Commitment to Privacy**

At Bitcoin SARL, we are committed to protect the privacy of our users.  We will do our best to ensure that any private information you provide us or that we collect as a result of your visit to our website is treated appropriately. This privacy policy explains our principles and procedures.

**2.        The Information We Collect About You and How We Use It**

When you enter our website, we automatically collect and store certain information such as:

Your IP address and domain name.

The type of browser and operating system you use.

The time of your visit.

The pages of our site you visit.

This information is used for administrative and technical purposes.  Such purposes could include counting the number of visitors to our site and individual pages within the site, determining referral sources to our website, assessing the technology used to access our site, and assisting with site maintenance

If you register on our website, we will collect personal information that you provide.  To register, you will be required to create a user name and account password and provide your name, mailing address, telephone number, email address and possibly other personal and/or business information.  When you sign in, you will have to supply your email address and password.

**3.        Information You Post**

You can review businesses and comment on the Website.  Please note that once you post a review or comment, it becomes part of the public conversation.  Your reviews and comments are not private.

**4.        Account and Password Information**

You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account and password and for restricting access to your computer, and you agree to accept responsibility for all activities that occur under your account or password.

**5.        Third-Party Links and Advertising**

Our website may contain third-party advertising and links to third-party websites that are not controlled by us.  The third-party advertising and links are made available to our readers as a convenience.  Please be aware that Bitcoin SARL, is not responsible for the content of third-party advertising and websites, nor are we responsible for the privacy policy or practices of third-parties and their websites. Our Privacy Policy only applies to information we collect from you while you are actively in session with us.  If you should link to a third-party website from our website, we strongly encourage you to review and become familiar with that website’s privacy policy.

**6.        Cookie Usage**

In order to provide you with customized service, we make use of “cookies.”  Cookies are essentially files that help us identify your computer and respond to it.  We use cookies to save you time while using the website, remind us who you are, and provide a customized experience. Cookies also allow us to collect non-personally identifiable information from you, like which pages you visited and what links you clicked on. In addition, we may use third party advertising companies to display advertisements on our website.  As part of their service, they may place separate cookies on your computer. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by our website only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertiser. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you may be able to modify your browser settings to decline cookies.  You may disable cookies on your own computer, but you may not be able to use some of the website functions unless cookies are enabled.

**7.        Your Right to See and Correct Information**

If you wish to see the information we collect about you, please contact us at privacy@bitcoinsarl.fr.  If you feel the information is incorrect, please send any corrections to us at privacy@bitcoinsarl.fr.  We will either update your information or include your correction with any information we store or use.

**8.        No Email Requests for Personal Information **

As you know, consumers are increasingly targeted by unscrupulous persons attempting to acquire sensitive personal or financial information, by impersonating legitimate businesses. We will never send you an unsolicited email or other communication requesting your private information. If you receive a communication directing you to enter your personal information, please disregard the instruction and contact us immediately at privacy@bitcoinsarl.fr.

**9.       Encryption and Authentication **

We take security seriously and take numerous precautions to protect the security of personally identifiable information. You can access your personally identifiable information on our website through a password and your email address. This password is encrypted. We recommend that you do not share your password with anyone. In addition, your personally identifiable information resides on a secure server that only selected personnel and contractors have access to. We encrypt certain sensitive information using technology to ensure that your personally identifiable information is safe as it is transmitted to us.

No data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we employ commercially reasonable security measures to protect data and seek to partner with companies which do the same, we cannot guarantee the security of any information transmitted to or from the website, and are not responsible for the actions of any third parties that may receive any such information.

**10.      Limited Disclosure**

From time to time, we may engage third-parties to assist in providing marketing, back-end, programming and support services.  These third-parties will only have access to information to the extent necessary to provide such services.  Except as specified above, we do not intend to disclose any personal information about you to any third-party without prior consent unless we have a good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (i) complete your transaction; (ii) comply with legal process or other legal requirements of any governmental authority; (iii) protect and defend our rights or property; and (iv) enforce the terms and conditions on this website.  We may provide certain information in aggregate form collected from, and relating to, you to third-parties.  However, we will not provide any personally identifying information.

We may share your information in a business transfer. As with any other business, we could merge with, or be acquired by, another company. If this occurs, the successor company would acquire the information we maintain, including personally identifiable information. However, personally identifiable information would remain subject to this Privacy Policy.

**11.      Reservation of Rights **

We may change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the revised Privacy Policy in the “Privacy Policy” section of the website. The revised Privacy Policy is effective immediately when posted on the website. It is the responsibility of each user to review the website and the Privacy Policy periodically to learn of any revisions to this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the website after the effectiveness of such revisions will constitute your acknowledgment and acceptance of the terms of the revised Privacy Policy.

**12.      How to Contact Us**

If you have questions about our privacy policy, please contact us:

By email:  privacy@bitcoinsarl.fr

By mail:

Bitcoin SARL  
9 Rue Emmanuel Philibert  
06300 Nice  
France

**2 December 2013**
